a beginner probably
you would say to yourself that
you're still learning the basics of growing plants
you're excited to gain more experience
you still rely on on videos and advice from others
slowly building your confidence
in growing different type of plants
or would you consider yourself
to be at the intermediate level?
you've been growing plants for a while
you're comfortable with the basics
you regularly grow a variety of plants
you can identify and solve common problems with plants
you have a solid
understanding of gardening and farming
and you're always learning new techniques
to improve your results
expert gardener or farmer
you've been gardening for many years
but probably many years don't mean anything
because just stick with one type of plant
probably just a few dozen plants
an expert
people often come to you for advice
you're confident managing plant care
you're confident managing propagation
pests and production
you enjoy sharing the knowledge you
you enjoy experimenting with advanced methods
which would you consider yourself to be?
choose. Beginner ? at the intermediate level?
or would you consider yourself to be an expert?